<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>eukaryota.cx</title>
<link>https://eukaryota.cx</link>
<description>lamp-post bulletin for eukaryotes</description>
<language>en</language>
<item>
<title>long abandoned refineries made into homes for hungry rats</title>
<link>https://eukaryota.cx/posts/2023/autumn/long-abandoned-refineries/</link>
<pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
<guid>https://eukaryota.cx/posts/2023/autumn/long-abandoned-refineries/</guid>
<description>			
		&lt;p&gt;hello.&lt;/p&gt;	
				&lt;p&gt;more and more often lately, i've been thinking about being impaled through the back, with a sword - as if i am a weakened leaf whose body could be ripped apart by the wind in mere seconds. however, i would like to set the record straight, to those of you with mind-reading capabilities: my body is &lt;em&gt;actually&lt;/em&gt; made of several strung up pieces of rusty sheet metal. are you vaccinated? NO? don't touch me! you'll get tetanus!!!&lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;figure&gt;
				&lt;video controls="" preload="none"&gt;
					&lt;source src="https://yewtu.be/latest_version?id=aSZb5yrayfE&amp;itag=22&amp;hmac_key=a6cc2ba0161a4182dd5665c4d2cce60d18e1ae16" type="video/mp4; codecs="avc1.42001e,mp4a.40.2""&gt;
				&lt;/video&gt;				
				&lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;sup&gt;&lt;em&gt;Jiyuu no Tori - Bird Of Freedom (Haibane Renmei)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
				&lt;/figure&gt;

				&lt;p&gt;and, you know -  as a heap of sheet metal, i observe. the wind, the snow, the moving mountains. slowly rotting here is, in a way, comforting. do you think this is how the mold spores feel, under your floorboards, listening to you eat your dinner? or how gilled fish must feel, suffocating under the noses of grabby fishermen?&lt;/p&gt;	
				
				&lt;blockquote&gt; 𓆞 - "It's the end. What a beautiful new place, this is..."&lt;/blockquote&gt;
				&lt;blockquote&gt; 𓍊𓋼𓍊𓋼𓍊 - "☸✝k☯%cc🌫b🌫🌥n⛈🕸" &lt;sup&gt;(the text is indiscernible. however, if listened to carefully enough, a faint hum can be heard.)&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
				&lt;p&gt;there's something so special about it. i love it so much. i love it as much as i hate it. i love these feelings, these physical callings. especially those that choose to ementate so intensely from the places that evoke them. places left to be abandoned; torn down, forgotten, broken, dangerous. do not touch them. do not walk here with bare feet. do not enter. do not succomb to curiosity. do not sprout wings. you dare attempt the climb? do not. do not. do.&lt;/p&gt; 

				&lt;p&gt;oil refineries at night look like cities of their own. housing built for machines fit to purpose. lamp posts for no one but the moths at Distillation Tower #6, who'll soon pass away from the toxic gas. places of opportunity for spirits out of luck. a burial ground for eukaryotes. don't we live in such a wonderful world? do not enter. you will get tetanus.&lt;/p&gt;

				&lt;figure&gt;
				&lt;img alt="a photo of a passing train on traintracks, with a beautifully lit refinery on the landscape. it looks like a city, in its distance and size." src="img2.png" loading="lazy"&gt;
				&lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;sup&gt;&lt;em&gt;a currently active refinery, soon to be made into a home for hungry rats&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
				&lt;/figure&gt;
				
				&lt;p&gt;anyway - i do not know how you got here, but i'm glad you are. this website, while doing its best, does not have much to speak of, as of writing. if you do not have one already, it would be worth your time to &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://github.com/yang991178/fluent-reader"&gt;set up&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://lzone.de/liferea/"&gt;an RSS&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://nodetics.com/feedbro/"&gt;reader.&lt;/a&gt; you can &lt;a href="../../../../feed.xml"&gt;add eukaryota.cx to it&lt;/a&gt;, so that you're notified whenever there's something new. you also can hook a bunch of other websites into it, like your own little personal bird feed, except the birds are your retinas and they're pecking at really cool words!!! &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.nononsenseapps.feeder.play"&gt;there are even &lt;/a&gt;&lt;a target="_blank" href="https://netnewswire.com/"&gt;mobile apps &lt;/a&gt;for this stuff. it is worth your time.&lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;p&gt;let me do you one better, before you go: here are a few really cool blogs with RSS feeds. maybe you've heard of them? i'm certain they'd love to hear of you!&lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;ul&gt;
					&lt;li&gt;&lt;a target="_blank"href="https://sizeof.cat"&gt;sizeof(cat)&lt;/a&gt; is a blog written by a strung up corsair cat about development, security, privacy, and other cat-aligned interests, such as &lt;a href="https://sizeof.cat/post/cyberpunk/"&gt;the entire genre of cyberpunk.&lt;/a&gt; i particularly enjoy their posts about music.&lt;/li&gt;
					&lt;li&gt;&lt;a target="_blank" href="https://xrafstar.monster/blog"&gt;xrafstar.monster&lt;/a&gt; is the home of Porpentine Charity Heartscape, known for her beautifully prosed torture porn, among other things. this website pairs particularly well with stimulants.&lt;/li&gt;
					&lt;li&gt;&lt;a target="_blank" href="https://maia.crimew.gay/"&gt;maia arson crimew&lt;/a&gt; is a swiss developer semi-recently known for leaking the TSA's no-fly list. posts here involve topics like opsec and leak analysis. when you visit this website, a little oneko-styled cat follows your mouse pointer around. nothing beats this!!!&lt;/li&gt;
					&lt;li&gt;the person who runs &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://brr.fyi/about"&gt;brr.fyi&lt;/a&gt; is an IT worker living on a semi-remote station in antarctica. places like this are the ones that you'll typically visit when dreaming and entering an alternate reality. life here is fascinating to read about, i think!&lt;/li&gt;
				&lt;/ul&gt;
				&lt;p&gt;that's all for now. have i soothed your nerves? see you soon.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
