<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>eukaryota.cx</title>
<link>https://eukaryota.cx</link>
<description>lamp-post bulletin for eukaryotes</description>
<language>en</language>

<item>
<title>Vinum Memoriae Mors</title>
<link>https://eukaryota.cx/posts/2023/winter/vinum-memoriae-mors/</link>
<pubDate>Sun, 08 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
<guid>https://eukaryota.cx/posts/2023/winter/vinum-memoriae-mors/</guid>
<description>		
				&lt;header&gt; 
					&lt;h1&gt;Vinum Memoriae Mors&lt;/h1&gt;
					&lt;div class="meta"&gt;
					&lt;span id="tags"&gt;&lt;em&gt;winter 2023 // klassje&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
					&lt;/div&gt;
				&lt;/header&gt;

				&lt;p&gt;Earlier this year, for several months in a row, I dreamt about eating other people.&lt;/p&gt;

				&lt;p&gt;Not that I &lt;em&gt;wanted&lt;/em&gt; to, of course. Not out of a great hunger, or a desire for cannibalism. No, I was eating people in my dreams because some part of me was longing. I wanted - *needed* to find what I was looking for. It never mattered what specifically it was. Only that... like love, it was more important than anything. An exceedingly deep yearning.&lt;/p&gt;

				&lt;p&gt;I'll never forget the last of these dreams I had, before they stopped completely - no context, no story, no environment. Only a woman, blonde - her eyes colourless, her body odorless -  beautiful, but collapsed, in the bright void. Then, me, barely aware of my own presence, clawing at her stomach. Clawing away at her skin, peeling at it; her blood digging underneath my nails, seeping into my cuticles while I was tearing out her arteries, her organs, digging at her body, as if it were a sandbox; helplessly trying to find the toy that I'd lost in the sand. It was empty. I could have reached the other side of her, made a hole straight through, and kept on digging. Her body could have been reduced to nothing, and I would have continued digging, biting, tearing; attempting to unearth it. The love. The meaning. The peace, the care, the heart.&lt;/p&gt;

				&lt;p&gt;But... I couldn't. I never could. Could you? Can anyone?&lt;/p&gt;
		

				&lt;section class="code"&gt;
				
					&lt;blockquote&gt;What's the earliest memory you have?&lt;/blockquote&gt;
					
					&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;"i.. don't know..."&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
					
					&lt;blockquote&gt;Try to remember.&lt;/blockquote&gt;

					&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;"i think... i'm in a house. a dining room? there are people all around. it's hazy, grey - bright, but dark. there's wallpaper on the walls, and a birthday cake. a kitchen to the right, the front door ahead, and a living room to the left."&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

					&lt;blockquote&gt;Move forward and open the front door.&lt;/blockquote&gt;

					&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;"i walk forward, open the door, and look outside. it's dark. there are bright lights shining above. in a distant yard, a dog is barking. they're celebrating."&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

					&lt;blockquote&gt;The sky? What do you see?&lt;/blockquote&gt;

					&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;"saturn. it's the emitting the most vibrant orange i've ever seen. it looks like Her rings are pulsing. beautiful bright orange streaks. spheres. sparks. i'm..."&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

					&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;"there are no stars. is this the end of the world?"&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

					&lt;blockquote&gt;Grab a pen. Show me.&lt;/blockquote&gt;

					&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;"i remember taking the photo. they called it Death's Saturn. they asked me what i was doing, and i... i was taking a photo of the explosions in the sky. how pretty they were. so... so beautiful."&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
	
				&lt;/section&gt;	
			
				&lt;p&gt;Some of these dreams were so interconnected that I found it hard to believe they weren't real. Gateways into other worlds. It was a part of the daily musing, the ephemera - "I wonder what the other side is up to?", I would think, before going back to an empty mind.&lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;p&gt;The same people kept showing up. These strangers, the people in my dreams - they were familiar, in the sense that they'd shown up in several other dreams before. They &lt;em&gt;remembered&lt;/em&gt; me, remembered what I did in those dreams. I'd never seen them before, either. They weren't known to me, and yet... they were everything.&lt;/p&gt;
			
				&lt;p&gt;Then, one night, they left me. I had done something terrible, upset them deeply. I lived with them; saw glimpses of it, every few nights. I loved them. I would never hurt them. Is other side me a bad person? Am I good, here? Am I bad on every other world? Is this where I'm supposed to be?&lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;p&gt;I never saw them in my dreams after that. They left me in the middle of a street, kicked me out of their apartment and drove off in their black van. This worl-&lt;/p&gt;

				&lt;section class="code"&gt;
				
				&lt;blockquote&gt;-doesn't belong to us. To you.&lt;/blockquote&gt;
				
				&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;"come oooooon! we should take it. make it ours. don't you want something interesting to happen for once? can't you be *interesting*? aren't you *interested*?"&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

				&lt;blockquote&gt;I really think this is-&lt;/blockquote&gt;

				&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;"i'm so sick of you, of this. aren't you curious? who this person that you've become? there's... so much here. don't you want to see wonder? to gawk? and love? and breathe? and taste!? ONE step. you can't do that?"&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

				&lt;blockquote&gt;No. You don't know. Breathing the air is taxing enough. I have authority here. Drop it.&lt;/blockquote&gt;

				&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;"..."&lt;/p&gt;

				&lt;p&gt;"i suppose curiousity requires bravery. i'm sorry for assuming you still had any."&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

				&lt;/section&gt;

				&lt;p&gt;I don't remember my earliest memory. Not like them. Every few years the memory hole dries up, and I can only remember the last year or four. The senescence of it all. I don't feel old, but my brain does. Vinum memoriae mors. I don't drink, but I dream. I see your eager teeth, and I think: "Huh. I ought to get a tooth sharpener." Wine is the death of memory. Perhaps dreams are the memory of death?&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
